

profile

- +90 530 147 80 79
- aliberkbatur@gmail.com
- m www.alibatur.info
- ♀ Konak / İZMİR

education

Prehistory Front-End Developer Istanbul University - Istanbul 2011 - 2019

High Scholl - Math Derici Mustafa Gürbüz Anadolu Lisesi Aydın 2007 - 2011

skills

CSS JavaScript Vue.js Nuxt.js Scrum iQuery

Agile Methods React.js Next.js Seo Photoshop MySQL& PHP

Web Design

hobies

HTML5

Video Games, Comic books, Motorcycles, Football, Ancient Humans and History

ALÍ BERK BATUR

Front-End Developer

about me

I was born in Istambul in 1993, I made and involved many projects of Front-End since 2013. HTML-MTMM. coding, CSS3 designing and animations, Responsive and Cross-Browser adaptability, JavaScript developing, also since few years i'm working with Yue, js and React. js. My priority about design is following the web-tecnologies up to date and thanks to that designing the websites in a very interactive way by the help of flow and the discrepancy principles. I can use Sclenium Webdriver for testing also. On the Backend side i can develop some basic Sol queries and PMp. I worked with Scrum and Kanban that i'm familiar with Anile Methodologies, Also i can work remotely with using ofithed and Jita.

experiences

Witty Commerce / Sr. Front-End Developer

Anril 2019 - Still

Front-end development for the Salesforce and Adobe Experience Manager Platforms (e-commerce)

I have involved www.loccitane.com and www.beko.com./es-es projects.

Blacc Enterprises/ Front-End Developer

November 2018 - April 2019

Front-End Development for www.cart.com.tr, e-commerce project.

I build the Nuxt.js application based on Vue.js and Es6 for the Store Front
I also lead the Front-End tream there.

Codespace Software / Front-End Developer

May 2018 - October 2018. Front-End Development React, React-Redux with ES6.

Project is www.ozan.com, a online wallet.

Evrim Yazılım Danışmanlık / Front-End Developer
October 2016 - May 2018

Front-End Development Vue.js, Vuex and Javascript with ES6.

Project is www.webgumruk.com a customs reportment page.

And also i built www.cepqumruk.com and so many mailing templates there.

Dugun.com / Front-End Developer

I worked there as a Scrum Master also.

2013 - 2015

Making HTML e-mail templates and some UI remakes.

licences

- Web programming with PHP basics, MYSQL and JavaScript
- Foundation of Programming / Object Oriented Design
- Accelerated ES6 JavaScript training
 Accelerated JavaScript training
- Vue.js training
- Step by step JavaScript